const STORE = [
    {
        question : "What is the name of the protagonists of the Anime 'Majokko Megu-chan'?",
        answers: [
            "Megu and Non",
            "Bia and Noa",
            "Catherine and Juliette",
            "Sugar and Rune"
    ], 
        correctAnswer: "Megu and Non"
    },
    {
        question : "In which era does the story of Manga 'Here comes Miss Modern' takes place?",
        answers: [
            "Meiji era",
            "Edo era",
            "Taisho era",
            "Heian era"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Taisho era"
    },
    {
        question : "In 'Sailor Moon' who are the Soldiers of the Outer Solar System? ",
        answers: [
            "Jupiter, Neptune, Uranus",
            "Pluto, Galaxia, Andromeda",
            "Uranus, Venus, Mars", 
            "Neptune, Pluto, Saturn"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Neptune, Pluto, Saturn"
    }, 
    {
        question : "In the Anime 'Creamy Mami, the Magic Angel' who grants the power to the protagonist, Yu? ",
        answers: [
            "Pino Pino",
            "Palo Palo",
            "Palo Palo",
            "Puru Puru"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Pino Pino"
    },
    {
        question : "What’s the name of the Protagonist of the Anime 'Daitarn 3'?",
        answers: [
            "Haran Flute",
            "Haran Jazz",
            "Haran Banjo",
            "Haran Piano"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Haran Banjo"   
    },
    {
        question : "In the Manga 'Hokuto no Ken', the protagonist is the successor of which famous School? ",
        answers: [
            "Nanto",
            "Goshasei",
            "Seito",
            "Hokuto"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Hokuto"
    },

    {
        question : "Who’s the Author of the famous Manga 'Galaxy Express 999'?",
        answers: [
            "Leiji Matsumoto",
            "Akira Toriyama",
            "Yoshihiro Togashi",
            "Go Nagai"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Leiji Matsumoto"
    },
    
    {
        question : "In the Manga 'Tokimeki Tonight', which type of monster is the mother of Ranze?" ,
        answers: [
            "A vampire",
            "A ghost",
            "A werewolf",
            "A zombie"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A werewolf"
    },
    {
        question : "In the Anime “Yattaman', what is the name of the main Villain female? ",
        answers: [
            "Tonzura",
            "Dokurobei",
            "Boyacky",
            "Doronjo"
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Doronjo"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the nationality of Roberto Hongo, coach in 'Captain Tsubasa'?",
        answers: [
            "Venezuelan",
            "Portorican",
            "Spanish", 
            "Brazilian"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Brazilian"
    }
];